National Weather Service Office, Surface weather observations at the Tucson International Airport records 1975-
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
National Weather Service Office, Surface weather observations at the Tucson International Airport records 1975-
MS 302
United States. Weather Service.
Logs of the National Weather Service's hourly surface weather observations at the Tucson International Airport. Logs contain carbon copies of holographic records in chronological order, with one volume per year.
4 linear feet
Special Collections, University Libraries University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL: http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/
Restrictions
None.
Historical Note
The National Weather Service is under the U.S. Dept. of Commerce, National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration.
Scope and Content Note
Logs of the National Weather Service's hourly surface weather observations at the Tucson International Airport. Logs contain carbon copies of holographic records in chronological order, with one volume per year.
Each volume contains one year's daily and hourly weather observations arranged in chronological order. Each month's surface weather observations are preceded by preliminary local climatological data reports which summarize the daily observations. Local climatological data reports include daily temperature, precipitation, wind and sunshine figures and monthly averages and totals. Surface weather observations record hourly observations for each day. Included are humidity, precipitation, pressure, temperature, dew point, wind and altimeter readings, and sky and ceiling, cloud cover and visibility observations along with special remarks.
Access Terms
United States -- National Weather Service Office, Tucson International Airport -- Archives
Meteorological stations -- Arizona -- Tucson
Weather -- Statistics
Tucson (Ariz.) -- Climate -- Observations
Logbooks
Container List
- Surface weather observations. 1975 (Volume 1)
- Surface weather observations. 1976 (Volume 2)
- Surface weather observations. 1977 (Volume 3)
- Surface weather observations. 1978 (Volume 4)
- Surface weather observations. 1979 (Volume 5)
- Surface weather observations. 1980 (Volume 6)
- Surface weather observations. 1981 (Volume 7)
- Surface weather observations. 1982 (Volume 8)
- Surface weather observations. 1983 (Volume 9)
- Surface weather observations. 1984 (Volume 10)
- Surface weather observations. 1985 (Volume 11)
- Surface weather observations. 1986 (Volume 12)
- Surface weather observations. 1987 (Volume 13)